

export const Questions =[{
    prompt:"Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",

    optionA: "npx create-react-app appname", 
    optionB :"npm install create-react-app",
    optionC :"npx install create-react-app -g",
    optionD :"install â€“ l create-react-app",


    Answer: "A",
   
},{

    prompt:"In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
    optionA:"Create",
    optionB:"Extends",
    optionC:"Inherits",
    optionD :"Delete",

    Answer:"B",



},
    
{
    prompt:"What is the default port number in which the application run ?",

    optionA:"3000",
    optionB:"8080",
    optionC:"5000",
    optionD :"3030",

    Answer:"A",
},
{
    prompt:"Which of the following valid component return type of React ?",

    optionA:"2",
    optionB:"3",
    optionC:"1",
    optionD :"5",

        Answer:"C,"
},{
    prompt:"Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",

    optionA:"State & Props",
    optionB:"Services & Components",
    optionC:"State & Services",
    optionD :"State & Component",

    Answer:"A",
},{
    prompt:"Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",

    optionA:"SetinitialComponent",
    optionB:"renderComponent",
    optionC:"render",
    optionD :"All of the above",


    Answer: "B",

},{
    prompt:"Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",

    optionA:"Compiler",
    optionB:"Transpilar",
    optionC:"Both of the above",
    optionD :"None of the above",


    Answer:"C",
},{
    prompt:"In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",

    optionA:"SetState",
    optionB:"Render with arguments",
    optionC:"Props",
    optionD :"Props Types",

    Answer:"C",
},
{
    prompt:"Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",

    optionA:"this.State{}",
    optionB:"this.setState",
    optionC:"this.setChangeState",
    optionD :"All of the above",


    Answer:"B",
},
{
    prompt:"Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",

    optionA:"self()",
    optionB:"inherits()",
    optionC:"this()",
    optionD :"super()",

    Answer:"D",
},

]